<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<manifest>
    <application>
        <name>Fall Detector</name>
        <short_name>FD</short_name>
        <app_status>TYPE_SAFETY_APP</app_status>
        <app_description>
        The Fall Detector app is designed to detect falls among the elderly. The 
        app detects a fall by subscribing to the accelerometer with a 10 Hz sampling rate. 
        To differentiate a fall from other daily activities, we use a two-stage process. 
        First, the app detects the free-fall stage, during which the vector sum of the 
        three-axis data should be less than a low-threshold. The free-fall causes the 
        transition from the Monitoring state to the WaitShock state. Second, the App 
        detects when the body impacts the ground, during which the vector sum should be 
        greater than a high-threshold. The impact triggers the transition from WaitShock 
        to Possible state. Because both free-fall and impact can happen in a long accelerometer 
        data buffer, the app can also transit from Monitoring to Possible. People tend to 
        make some movement and then remain still after the impact. The Possible and StillCounter 
        counters capture such a sequence. Finally, if the person remains still for a certain timeout, 
        the app will transition to the FallConfirm state.
        </app_description>
    </application>
    
    <permissions>
        <api name="AmuletSubscribeInternalSensor" first_argument="ACCELEROMETER" />
        <api name="AmuletPutData" />
        <api name="AmuletGetAccelValue" />
        <api name="AmuletDisplayClr" />
        <api name="AmuletDisplayMessage" />
        <api name="AmuletStateTransition" />
        <api name="AmuletITOA" />
        <api name="AmuletGetAccelX" />
        <api name="AmuletGetAccelY" />
        <api name="AmuletGetAccelZ" />
        <api name="AmuletSetFont" />
        <api name="AmuletConcat" />
        <api name="AmuletTextHeight" />
        <api name="AmuletClearRect" />
        <api name="AmuletCenteredText" />
        <api name="AmuletPushChangesToDisplay" />
        <api name="AmuletDrawFastVLine" />
        <api name="AmuletDrawFastHLine" />
        <api name="AmuletFillRect" />
        <api name="AmuletRegularCenteredText" />
        <api name="AmuletBoldCenteredText" />
    </permissions>
</manifest>
